{
  "questionList": {
    "question1": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "answer": "Motera Stadium",
        "question": "Which is the Largest cricket stadium in the world?",
        "option1": "Melbourne Cricket Ground",
        "option2": "Motera Stadium",
        "option3": "Lords Stadium"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "answer": "Rafael Nadal",
        "question": "what is the full name of Nadal?",
        "option1": "Rafael Nadal",
        "option2": "Rafeal Nadal",
        "option3": "Rathod Nadal"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "answer": "1987",
        "question": "When did Maria Sharapova born?",
        "option1": "1988",
        "option2": "1986",
        "option3": "1987"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "answer": "15",
        "question": "How many players are required in Rugby?",
        "option1": "15",
        "option2": "11",
        "option3": "12"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "answer": "9",
        "question": "How many Indians won the nobel prize?",
        "option1": "9",
        "option2": "11",
        "option3": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "answer": "Australia",
        "question": "Which Country has won world cup maximum times?",
        "option1": "Australia",
        "option2": "WestIndies",
        "option3": "England"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "answer": "19",
        "question": "How Many guinees world records are under Sachin Name?",
        "option1": "20",
        "option2": "19",
        "option3": "18"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "answer": "Ravi Shastri",
        "question": "Who is the first indian player who have hit 6 sixes in an over?",
        "option1": "Ravi Shastri",
        "option2": "Yuvaraj Singh",
        "option3": "Sachin Tendulkar"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "answer": "London",
        "question": "Where did 2012 olympics held?",
        "option1": "Rio",
        "option2": "London",
        "option3": "Tokyo"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "answer": "Tennies",
        "question": "Vishwanathan Anand is not belongs to which sport?",
        "option1": "Chess",
        "option2": "Tennies",
        "option3": "Golf"
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "answer": "Germany",
        "question": "Ussain Bolt is not from this country?",
        "option1": "Jamaica",
        "option2": "Germany",
        "option3": "Poland"
      },
      {
        "id": 12,
        "answer": "9.58 Seconds",
        "question": "How Many seconds is Ussain Bolt's world Record in 100 metres?",
        "option1": "9.58 Seconds",
        "option2": "9.57 Seconds",
        "option3": "9.59 Seconds"
      },
      {
        "id": 13,
        "answer": "10 Meter Air Rifle",
        "question": "Abhinav Bindra won the gold medal in olympics under which game?",
        "option1": "10 Meter Air Rifle",
        "option2": "20 Meter Air Rifle",
        "option3": "15 Meter Air Rifle"
      },
      {
        "id": 14,
        "answer": "3",
        "question": "How many times London Hosted Olympics?",
        "option1": "4",
        "option2": "2",
        "option3": "3"
      },
      {
        "id": 15,
        "answer": "Pakistan",
        "question": "Where did Milkha singh born?",
        "option1": "India",
        "option2": "Pakistan",
        "option3": "Nepal"
      },
      {
        "id": 16,
        "answer": "Chess",
        "question": "Magnus Carlsen belongs to which sport?",
        "option1": "Golf",
        "option2": "Tennis",
        "option3": "Chess"
      },
      {
        "id": 17,
        "answer": "Novak Djokovic",
        "question": "Wimbeldon 2019 Winner Male?",
        "option1": "Novak Djokovic",
        "option2": "Roger Federer",
        "option3": "Rafael Nadal"
      },
      {
        "id": 18,
        "answer": "Simona Halep",
        "question": "Wimbeldon 2019 Winner Female?",
        "option1": "Serena Williams",
        "option2": "Simona Halep",
        "option3": "Sania Mirza"
      },
      {
        "id": 19,
        "answer": "3 idiots",
        "question": "Which Indian Movie was not played at RoyalAlbertHall,London?",
        "option1": "Bahubali",
        "option2": "3 idiots",
        "option3": "Saho"
      },
      {
        "id": 20,
        "answer": "Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna",
        "question": "Which is the highest award in Indian Sport Industry?",
        "option1": "Dadasaheb Phalke Award",
        "option2": "Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna",
        "option3": "Padma Sri"
      },
      {
        "id": 21,
        "answer": "Srisaila Sri Rajamouli",
        "question": "What is the Full name of Rajamouli?",
        "option1": "Srisaila Sri Rajamouli",
        "option2": "Srisaila Sai Rajamouli",
        "option3": "Srisaila Sagar Rajamouli"
      },
      {
        "id": 22,
        "answer": "Dada",
        "question": "Other Name of sourav ganguly is?",
        "option1": "Dumbo",
        "option2": "Dadda",
        "option3": "Dada"
      },
      {
        "id": 23,
        "answer": "Roger Federer",
        "question": "Who wons most grand slam titles",
        "option1": "Roger Federer",
        "option2": "Rafael Nadal",
        "option3": "Novak Djokovic"
      },
      {
        "id": 24,
        "answer": "Michael Phelps",
        "question": "Who has the most Olympic medals of all time?",
        "option1": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "option2": "Michael Phelps",
        "option3": "Usain Bolt"
      },
      {
        "id": 25,
        "answer": "Felix Mendelssohn",
        "question": "Who wrote the Wedding March?",
        "option1": "Geroge Harrison",
        "option2": "Felix Mendelssohn",
        "option3": "J K Rowling"
      },
      {
        "id": 26,
        "answer": "30,000",
        "question": "What is the seating capacity of the lords stadium?",
        "option1": "34,000",
        "option2": "32,000",
        "option3": "30,000"
      },
      {
        "id": 27,
        "answer": "Kane Williamson",
        "question": "Who won player of the series for 2019 Cricket world cup?",
        "option1": "Rohit Sharma",
        "option2": "Kane Williamson",
        "option3": "Shane Watson"
      },
      {
        "id": 28,
        "answer": "1",
        "question": "How many times does England won cricket world cup?",
        "option1": "2",
        "option2": "3",
        "option3": "1"
      },
      {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "Phil Mickelson became the oldest sportsperson to win a major championship in which sports?",
        "option1": "Tennis",
        "option2": "Squash",
        "option3": "Golf",
        "answer": "Golf"
      },
      {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "Who is the winner of the womenâ€™s title of French Open tournament 2021?",
        "option1": "Barbora Krejcikova",
        "option2": "Naomi Osaka",
        "option3": "Jennifer Brady",
        "answer": "Barbora Krejcikova"
      },
      {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "Which country won the inaugural ICC World Test Championship (WTC)?",
        "option1": "New Zealand",
        "option2": "England",
        "option3": "Australia",
        "answer": "New Zealand"
      },
      {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "Which racing driver won the Formula One Belgian Grandprix Tournament?",
        "option1": "Lewis Hamilton",
        "option2": "Max Verstappen",
        "option3": "Sebastien Vettel",
        "answer": "Max Verstappen"
      },
      {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "What is the motto of the 2022 Winter Olympics and Paralympics?",
        "option1": "Together For a Shared Future",
        "option2": "Inclusive and Strong",
        "option3": "Sustainable Growth",
        "answer": "Together For a Shared Future"
      },
      {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "Garbine Muguruza, who won her first WTA Finals title recently, is from which country?",
        "option1": "Spain",
        "option2": "France",
        "option3": "USA",
        "answer": "Spain"
      }
    ]
  }
}
